Guide to the Austrian History Yearbook papers, 1959-1977 UA 015
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Austrian History Yearbook papers, 1959-1977; 231196
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Gordon, Bertram M. "The Challenge of Industrialization: The Catholic Church and the Working Class in and around Vienna, 1815-1848", 231246 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Kimball, Stanley B. "The Mormons in the Habsburg Lands, 1841-1914;" Wienzierl, Erika. "Comments;" Kimball. "Reply", 231245 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Austenson, Roy A. "Count Buol and the Metternich Tradition;" Heindl, Waltraud. "Comments", 231244 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Magosci, Paul R. "A Historiographical Guide to Subcarpathian Rus", 231243 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Komlos, John. "Dissertations on Hungarian History completed since 1920", 231242 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Kreissler, Felix. "Recently Published French Studies", 231241 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - "American Publications on Austrian History;" "Doctoral Dissertations on Austrian History in the United States and Canada;" "Present Research Projects on Austrian History in the United States and Canada", 231240 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 9-10 - Stourzh, Gerald. "Hugo Hantsch;" Beaber, Lawrence R. "Otakar Odlozilik;" Thalberg, Hans J. "Ludwig Kleinwaechter;" Kann, Robert A. "Otto Leichter;" Buehrig, Edward H.; Diamant, Alfred; Lambert, Louis E. "Vaclav Benes", 231239 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Preliminary Pages, table of contents, etc., 231238 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Rudolph, Richard L. "Thae Pattern of Austrian Industrial Growth from the Eighteenth to the Early Twentieth Century", 231237 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Marz, Eduard. "Comments;" Matis, Herbert. "Comments", 231236 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Rudolph, Richard L. "The New versus the Old in Austrian Economic History", 231235 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Rabinbach, Anson G. "The Migration of Galician Jews to Vienna, 1857-1880", 231234 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Stadler, Karl R. "Comments;" Hausler, Wolfgang. "Comments;" Eddie, Scott M. "Galician Jews as Migrants: An Alternative Hypothesis", 231233 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Fichtner, Paula Sutter. "When Brothers Agree: Bohemia, the Habsburgs, and the Schmalkadic Wars, 1546-1547;" Heiss, Gernot. "Comments;" Fichtner. "Reply", 231232 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Rock, Kenneth W. "Felix Schwarzenberg, Military Diplomat;" Rumpler, Helmut. "Comments;" Rock. "Reply", 231231 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Hanak, Peter. "Economics Society and Sociopolitical Thought in Hungarry during the Age of Capitalism;" Ranki, Gyorgy. "A Preliminary Study of the New Hungarian Historical Synthesis", 231230 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Ember, Gyozo. "The Hungarian Archives;" Sugar, Peter F. "Comments;" Ember. "Reply", 231229 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - Schroth, Hans; Herlitzka, Ernst K. "The Society for the History of the Working-Class Movement;" Kollman, Eric C. "Comments", 231228 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - "American Publications in Austrian History;" Doctoral Dissertations on Austrian History in the United States and Canada;" Present Research Projects on Austrian History in the United States and Canada", 231227 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - "Recent Austrian and German Books;" Austrian and German Periodical Literature;" Austrian Doctoral Dissertations on the History of Austria from 1520 to the Present;" A Select List of Recent Italian Publications", 231226 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 - "News from the United States;" "News from Austria and Germany", 231225 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 11 -Winters, Stanley B. "Frantisek Reubik;" Wandruszka, Adam. "Victor-Lucien Tapey;" Hitchins, Keith. "Lajos Jordaky;" Sweet, Paul R. "Max Brauback;" Rath. "S. Harriet Thomson", 231224 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Preliminary pages, etc., 231223 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Deak, Istvan. "Destruction, Revolution or Reform: Hungary on the Eve of 1848;" Gottas, Friedrich. "Comments;" Deak. "Reply", 231222 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Kiraly, Belak. "Ferenc Deak during the Vormaz Era;" Deak, Erno. "Comments;" Bak, Janos M. "Vivat Kossuth-Faute de Mieux?;" Kiraly. "Reply", 231221 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Deme, Laszlo. "Nationalism and Cosmopolitanism among the Hungarian Radicals;" Deak, Erno. "Comments;" Deme. "Reply", 231220 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Deak, Istvan. "Lajos Kossuth's Nationalism and Internationalism;" Gottas, Friedrich. "Comments;" Bodea, Cornelia. "Comments;" Deak. "Reply", 231219 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Zacek, Joseph F. "Czech Attitudes toward the Hungarian Revolution;" Koralkova, Kveta. "Comments;" Glettler, Monkia. "Comments;" Zacek. "Reply", 231218 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Deak, Istvan. "Istvan Szechenyi, Miklos Wesselenyi, Lajos Kossuth and the Problem of Romanian Nationalism;" Maior, Liviu; Teodor, Pompiliu. "Comments", 231217 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Florescu, Radu R. "Debunking a Myth: The Maygar-Romanian National Struggle of 1848-1849;" Peyfuss, Max Demeter. "Comments", 231216 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Roider, Karl A., Jr. "Futile Peacemaking: Austria and the Congress of Nemirov;" Vesolinovic, Rajko. "Comments;" Vocelka, Karl. "Comments;" Roider. "Reply", 231215 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Adler, Philip J. "Serbs, Maygars, and Staatinteresse in Eighteenth Century Austria: A Study in the History of Habsburg Administration;" Haselsteiner, Horst. "Comments;" Djordevic, Dimitrije. "Comments", 231214 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Reinerman, Alan J. "Metternich versus Chateaubriand; Austria, France and the Conclave of 1829;" Martina, Father Giacomo. "Comments;" Wienzerl, Erika. "Comments", 231213 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Wegs, J. Robert. "The Marshaling of Copper: An Index of Austro-Hungarian Economic Mobilization during World War I;" Mejzlik, Heinrich. "Comments", 231212 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Klemperer, Klemes von. "Ignaz Seipel as European Statesman;" Ableitinger, Alfred. "Comments;" Klemperer. "Reply", 231211 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Haag, John. "Othmar Spann and the Quest for a True State", 231210 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Pauley, Bruce F. "A Case Study in Fascism: The Styrian Heimatschutz and Austrian National Socialism;" Botz, Gerhard. "Comments;" Pauley. "Reply", 231209 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Low, Alfred D. "On the Eve of the February 1934 Uprising of the Austrian Socialist Workers;" Botz, Gerhard. "Comments", 231208 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Ranki, Gyorgy; Lacko, Miklos. "The Restoration and Crisis of Capitalism in Hungary, 1919-1944", 231207 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Orton, Lawrence D. "Polish Publications since 1945 on Austrian and Galician History, 1772-1918", 231206 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - "American Publication on Austrian History", 231205 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - "Doctoral Dissertations on Austrian History in the United States and Canada", 231204 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - "Present Research Projects on Austrian History in the United States and Canada", 231203 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - "Austrian and German Books;" "Austrian and German Periodical Literature", 231202 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - "Austrian Doctoral Dissertations on the History of Austria from 1520 to the Present;" "A Select List of Recent Italian Publications", 231201 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Kann, Robert A. "Ludwig Jedlicka;" Plaschka, Richard. "Kurt Wessely;" "Special Announcements", 231200 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Austrian News (not published), 231199 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - United States and Canadian News (not published), 231198 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Austrian History Yearbook, v. 12-13 - Miscellaneous notes, manuscripts, correspondence, 231197 (Box 6, Folder 34)